<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Mu&#39;s NoteBook</title>
  
  <subtitle>沐沐</subtitle>
  <link href="http://www.itmua.tk/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://www.itmua.tk/"/>
  <updated>2022-05-29T14:27:40.989Z</updated>
  <id>http://www.itmua.tk/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>沐沐</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>爱是什么？（中韩文版本）</title>
    <link href="http://www.itmua.tk/2022/05/27/%E7%88%B1%E6%98%AF%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%EF%BC%9F%E4%B8%AD%E9%9F%A9%E6%96%87%E7%89%88%E6%9C%AC/"/>
    <id>http://www.itmua.tk/2022/05/27/%E7%88%B1%E6%98%AF%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%EF%BC%9F%E4%B8%AD%E9%9F%A9%E6%96%87%E7%89%88%E6%9C%AC/</id>
    <published>2022-05-27T12:35:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-05-29T14:27:40.989Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="爱是什么？中韩文版本"><a href="#爱是什么？中韩文版本" class="headerlink" title="爱是什么？中韩文版本"></a>爱是什么？中韩文版本</h1><p>爱是什么？</p><p>사랑이 뭐예요?</p><p>爱是爱心，爱是美好的语言，爱是无私的奉献，爱会带给你无限的温暖，爱会带给你健康和快乐……</p><p>사랑은 사랑, 사랑은 아름다운 언어, 사랑은 사심없는 헌신, 사랑은 당신에게 무한한 따뜻함을 가져다 주고, 사랑은 당신에게 건강과 행복을 가져다 줍니다 …..</p><p>爱像春天的微风，吹动我们的心弦；爱就像心中的火焰，炽热又温暖。</p><p>사랑은 봄의 미풍처럼 우리의 심금을 울린다. 사랑은 마음속의 불꽃과 같고, 뜨겁고 따뜻하다.</p><p>爱是一物降一物，爱是甘拜下风，爱是雨中的一把伞，爱是讲不完的心事，说不尽的话。爱是念念不忘，爱是相互包容吗，爱是吵不散场，爱是不变质的水，爱是心甘情愿，爱是无缝衔接，爱是全身爱退。</p><p>사랑은 한 가지가 떨어지는 것이고, 사랑은 바람을 쐬는 것이고, 사랑은 빗속의 우산이고, 사랑은 끝없는 걱정거리이며, 끝없는 말을 한다. (조지 버나드 쇼, 사랑명언) 사랑은 잊지 않고, 사랑은 서로 포용하고, 사랑은 시끄럽고, 사랑은 변질되지 않는 물이고, 사랑은 기꺼이 하고, 사랑은 원활한 연결, 사랑은 온몸의 사랑이다. (조지 버나드 쇼, 사랑명언)</p><p>我不知道什么是爱，但是一定不是流不完的眼泪，不是傍晚的失眠。</p><p>나는 사랑이 무엇인지 모르지만, 반드시 흐를 수 없는 눈물이 아니라 저녁의 불면증이 아니다.</p><p>爱的定义太广泛了，我在雾中站了好久，我不明白什么是爱，没有什么爱不爱，爱会奋不顾身去拥抱你，爱不会在意他人的眼光，我不奢求爱，也不渴望爱。爱会在合适的时机出现，爱有真假，爱可以装出来。</p><p>사랑의 정의는 너무 광범위하다. 나는 안개 속에 오랫동안 서 있었다. 나는 사랑이 무엇인지 이해하지 못했다. 사랑하지 않는 것은 없다. 사랑은 몸을 돌보지 않고 너를 안아주고, 사랑은 다른 사람의 안목을 의식하지 않는다. 나는 사랑을 바라지 않는다. 사랑을 갈망하지도 않는다. (마하트마 간디, 사랑명언) 사랑은 적절한 시기에 나타나고, 사랑은 진짜와 거짓이 있고, 사랑은 가장할 수 있다.</p><p>爱不会是简简单单，爱是动词，爱是形容词，爱是来形容我们，爱是相互牵挂，爱是互相猜忌，爱是动名词的代表，爱即使明白结果也要追随，爱是信任，爱是依靠，爱是永不后悔。</p><p>사랑은 단순한 것이 아니다. 사랑은 동사다. 사랑은 형용사다. 사랑은 우리를 묘사하는 것이다. 사랑은 상호 걱정이다. 사랑은 상호 의심이다. 사랑은 동명사의 대표다. 사랑은 결과를 이해하더라도 따라야 한다. 사랑은 믿음이다. 사랑은 의지하고, 사랑은 결코 후회하지 않는다.</p><p>爱可以简简单单，但不能随随便便。爱是前人栽树后人乘凉。是勇敢者的游戏，一路仁至义尽，暗号是你听得到的心甘情愿，慈悲放过你，没放过你自己，雪地里写诗，是看不见的，蕴藏在心底里，没有定义。</p><p>사랑은 간단할 수 있지만 마음대로 해서는 안 된다. 사랑은 선인들이 나무를 심고 후세 사람들이 바람을 쐬는 것이다. 용감한 게임, 모든 방법 자비, 암호는 당신이 들을 수 있는 기꺼이, 자비가 당신을 놓아주고, 당신 자신을 놓아주지 않고, 눈밭에 시를 쓰는 것은 보이지 않고, 마음속에 감추어져 있고, 정의가 없다. (조지 버나드 쇼, 용기명언)</p><p>被爱的前提不应该是漂亮，优秀，可以是任何人。</p><p>사랑받는 전제는 아름답고 우수해서는 안 되며, 누구나 될 수 있다.</p><p>爱是本能，教不会，也强求不来。  </p><p>사랑은 본능이고, 가르치지도 않고, 강요하지도 않는다.   </p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;爱是什么？中韩文版本&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#爱是什么？中韩文版本&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;爱是什么？中韩文版本&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;爱是什么？中韩文版本&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;爱是什么？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;사랑이 뭐예요?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱是爱心，爱是美好</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="文学" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/categories/%E6%96%87%E5%AD%A6/"/>
    
    
    <category term="文学" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/tags/%E6%96%87%E5%AD%A6/"/>
    
    <category term="爱情" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/tags/%E7%88%B1%E6%83%85/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>爱是什么？（中日文版本）</title>
    <link href="http://www.itmua.tk/2022/05/27/%E7%88%B1%E6%98%AF%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%EF%BC%9F%E4%B8%AD%E6%97%A5%E6%96%87%E7%89%88%E6%9C%AC/"/>
    <id>http://www.itmua.tk/2022/05/27/%E7%88%B1%E6%98%AF%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%EF%BC%9F%E4%B8%AD%E6%97%A5%E6%96%87%E7%89%88%E6%9C%AC/</id>
    <published>2022-05-27T12:35:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-05-29T14:27:54.319Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="爱是什么？中日文版本"><a href="#爱是什么？中日文版本" class="headerlink" title="爱是什么？中日文版本"></a>爱是什么？中日文版本</h1><p>爱是什么？</p><p>愛とは何ですか？</p><p>爱是爱心，爱是美好的语言，爱是无私的奉献，爱会带给你无限的温暖，爱会带给你健康和快乐……</p><p>愛は愛であり、愛は美しい言葉であり、愛は無私の献身であり、愛はあなたに無限の暖かさをもたらし、愛はあなたに健康と幸福をもたらします ……。</p><p>爱像春天的微风，吹动我们的心弦；爱就像心中的火焰，炽热又温暖。</p><p>春のそよ風のように、私たちの琴線を揺さぶる； 愛は心の中の炎のようで、熱くて暖かい。</p><p>爱是一物降一物，爱是甘拜下风，爱是雨中的一把伞，爱是讲不完的心事，说不尽的话。爱是念念不忘，爱是相互包容吗，爱是吵不散场，爱是不变质的水，爱是心甘情愿，爱是无缝衔接，爱是全身爱退。</p><p>愛は何かを落とすことであり、愛は風下に甘んじることであり、愛は雨の中の傘であり、愛は語り尽くせない心配事であり、言い尽くせないことである。 愛は忘れないことです。愛は互いに包容し合うことですか。愛は騒がしくて散り散りにならないことです。愛は変質しない水です。愛は心から望んでいます。愛はシームレスにつながり、愛は全身愛が退きます。</p><p>我不知道什么是爱，但是一定不是流不完的眼泪，不是傍晚的失眠。</p><p>愛とは何かわかりませんが、きっと流しきれない涙ではなく、夕方の不眠ではありません。</p><p>爱的定义太广泛了，我在雾中站了好久，我不明白什么是爱，没有什么爱不爱，爱会奋不顾身去拥抱你，爱不会在意他人的眼光，我不奢求爱，也不渴望爱。爱会在合适的时机出现，爱有真假，爱可以装出来。</p><p>愛の定義が広すぎて、私は長い間霧の中に立っていました。愛とは何か分かりません。愛も愛していません。愛は身を粉にしてあなたを抱きしめます。愛は他人の目を気にしません。私は愛を求めません。愛も切望しません。 愛は適切なタイミングで現れます。愛には真偽があり、愛は装うことができます。</p><p>爱不会是简简单单，爱是动词，爱是形容词，爱是来形容我们，爱是相互牵挂，爱是互相猜忌，爱是动名词的代表，爱即使明白结果也要追随，爱是信任，爱是依靠，爱是永不后悔。</p><p>愛は簡単ではありません。愛は動詞であり、愛は形容詞であり、愛は私たちを形容するものであり、愛は互いに心配し合うものであり、愛は互いに推測し合うものであり、愛は動名詞の代表であり、愛は結果を理解しても追随しなければなりません。愛は信頼であり、愛は頼りであり、愛は決して後悔しません。</p><p>爱可以简简单单，但不能随随便便。爱是前人栽树后人乘凉。是勇敢者的游戏，一路仁至义尽，暗号是你听得到的心甘情愿，慈悲放过你，没放过你自己，雪地里写诗，是看不见的，蕴藏在心底里，没有定义。</p><p>愛は簡単ですが、勝手にしてはいけません。 愛は先人が木を植えて子孫を涼むことである。 勇敢な人の遊びです。仁を尽くして義を尽くします。暗号はあなたが聞くことができる喜んで、慈悲をもってあなたを見逃して、あなた自身を見逃すことはありません。雪の中に詩を書くことは、見えません。心の底に秘められています。定義はありません。</p><p>被爱的前提不应该是漂亮，优秀，可以是任何人。</p><p>愛される前提は美しく、優れているべきではなく、誰でもいい。</p><p>爱是本能，教不会，也强求不来。  </p><p>愛は本能であり、教えることも、強要することもできない。   </p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;爱是什么？中日文版本&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#爱是什么？中日文版本&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;爱是什么？中日文版本&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;爱是什么？中日文版本&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;爱是什么？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;愛とは何ですか？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱是爱心，爱是美好</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="文学" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/categories/%E6%96%87%E5%AD%A6/"/>
    
    
    <category term="文学" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/tags/%E6%96%87%E5%AD%A6/"/>
    
    <category term="爱情" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/tags/%E7%88%B1%E6%83%85/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>爱是什么？（中英文版本）</title>
    <link href="http://www.itmua.tk/2022/05/27/%E7%88%B1%E6%98%AF%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%EF%BC%9F%E4%B8%AD%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87%E7%89%88%E6%9C%AC/"/>
    <id>http://www.itmua.tk/2022/05/27/%E7%88%B1%E6%98%AF%E4%BB%80%E4%B9%88%EF%BC%9F%E4%B8%AD%E8%8B%B1%E6%96%87%E7%89%88%E6%9C%AC/</id>
    <published>2022-05-27T12:35:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-05-29T14:28:03.944Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="爱是什么？中英文版本"><a href="#爱是什么？中英文版本" class="headerlink" title="爱是什么？中英文版本"></a>爱是什么？中英文版本</h1><p>爱是什么？</p><p>What is love?</p><p>爱是爱心，爱是美好的语言，爱是无私的奉献，爱会带给你无限的温暖，爱会带给你健康和快乐……</p><p>Love is love, love is a beautiful language, love is selfless dedication, love will bring you infinite warmth, love will bring you health and happiness. ……</p><p>爱像春天的微风，吹动我们的心弦；爱就像心中的火焰，炽热又温暖。</p><p>Love is like the spring breeze, blowing our heartstrings; Love is like the flame in the heart, hot and warm.</p><p>爱是一物降一物，爱是甘拜下风，爱是雨中的一把伞，爱是讲不完的心事，说不尽的话。爱是念念不忘，爱是相互包容吗，爱是吵不散场，爱是不变质的水，爱是心甘情愿，爱是无缝衔接，爱是全身爱退。</p><p>Love has its vanquisher. Love is willing to bow down to the wind. Love is an umbrella in the rain. Love is endless worries and endless words. Is love unforgettable, is love tolerant of each other? Love is noisy, love is unchangeable water, love is willing, love is seamless, and love is full of love.</p><p>我不知道什么是爱，但是一定不是流不完的眼泪，不是傍晚的失眠。</p><p>I don’t know what love is, but it must not be endless tears or insomnia in the evening.</p><p>爱的定义太广泛了，我在雾中站了好久，我不明白什么是爱，没有什么爱不爱，爱会奋不顾身去拥抱你，爱不会在意他人的眼光，我不奢求爱，也不渴望爱。爱会在合适的时机出现，爱有真假，爱可以装出来。</p><p>The definition of love is too broad. I have been standing in the fog for a long time. I don’t know what love is, and there is nothing I don’t love. Love will give up my life to hug you. Love doesn’t care about other people’s eyes, and I don’t expect or desire love. Love will appear at the right time, love is true or false, and love can be faked.</p><p>爱不会是简简单单，爱是动词，爱是形容词，爱是来形容我们，爱是相互牵挂，爱是互相猜忌，爱是动名词的代表，爱即使明白结果也要追随，爱是信任，爱是依靠，爱是永不后悔。</p><p>Love is not simple, love is a verb, love is an adjective, love is used to describe us, love is mutual concern, love is mutual suspicion, love is the representative of gerunds, love should follow even if it knows the result, love is trust, love is dependence, and love is never regret.</p><p>爱可以简简单单，但不能随随便便。爱是前人栽树后人乘凉。是勇敢者的游戏，一路仁至义尽，暗号是你听得到的心甘情愿，慈悲放过你，没放过你自己，雪地里写诗，是看不见的，蕴藏在心底里，没有定义。</p><p>Love can be simple, but not casual. Love is when predecessors plant trees and later generations enjoy the cool. It’s a game of the brave. All the way, I show my utmost forbearance. The secret code is your willingness to hear. I will spare you with compassion and myself. Writing poetry in the snow is invisible, hidden in my heart and undefined.</p><p>被爱的前提不应该是漂亮，优秀，可以是任何人。</p><p>The premise of being loved should not be beautiful, excellent, but anyone.</p><p>爱是本能，教不会，也强求不来。  </p><p>Love is instinct, which can’t be taught or forced.   </p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;爱是什么？中英文版本&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#爱是什么？中英文版本&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;爱是什么？中英文版本&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;爱是什么？中英文版本&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;爱是什么？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is love?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱是爱心</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="文学" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/categories/%E6%96%87%E5%AD%A6/"/>
    
    
    <category term="文学" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/tags/%E6%96%87%E5%AD%A6/"/>
    
    <category term="爱情" scheme="http://www.itmua.tk/tags/%E7%88%B1%E6%83%85/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
